[Music]
welcome back to Bazaar Morning Call well
this morning the sgx Nifty is indicating
that the start will be in the green
about 30 odd points yesterday was a good
good day let's see if there is any
follow-on buying this morning the global
Handover was not too good so it could be
a tricky day to start with let's see ITC
is in focus it has acquired yoga bar a
brand that a lot of us are familiar with
among them over to you how does the
acquisition look well the acquisition
looks good from an addressable Market
standpoint but ITC will acquire you know
the owners of yoga bar entirely over the
next three to four years what they will
immediately do is 39.4 stake is what
they'll buy for about 175 Watt craws and
then over the next couple of years
they'll also add another 80 cross for a
total of 47.5 percent stake and this is
by March 31st 2025. the balance stake
will be acquired basis predefined
valuation criteria and this is something
that everyone will keep an eye out on
the addressable Market of healthy
snacking and health bars Etc is closer
around 5 45 000 crores and yoga bar FY
22 sales were close to around 68 odd
crores and a couple of years ago that
was just about 32 odd cross so it's a
fast growing Market as well tranche one
of the deal has been done at around six
and a half times yoga bars at 522 sales
slightly on the pricier side so let's
see uh you know the rate at which ITC
can scale this business but from their
standpoint the fact that it's a high
gross margin and a huge uh you know
addressable Market it is a mild positive
okay all right manglam thanks a lot for
that well let's get to some result
reactions we'll be joining you to tell
us but I say I say pro-life insurance
and I say I say Lombard's numbers survey
hi thanks for that so starting with
ICICI I prove strong numbers from the
company the change in the product makes
in the favor of annuity protection and
non-link savings has led to a vnb margin
of 34 which is 720 basis points higher
than Q3 fy22 this has also led to a vnb
growth of 20 at 618 crores ape which was
largely known came in weaker and that
was largely driven by shrinking ICICI
Bank share persistence has also improved
across the board AUM is up six percent
on a year-on-year basis and solvency has
also improved at 2.12 times the stock
should react positively the corn call is
today morning so we will watch out for
what the management is guiding moving on
to ICICI Lombard the company has
delivered a healthy 17 premium growth
led by health and fire Insurance the Pat
has come in at 11 growth slightly lower
than estimates due to lower investment
income the combined ratio was broadly
stable at 104 the ROI came in 14.3
percent similar to what it was same time
last year the management has guided for
a continued investments in the retail
Health business and decline in the
combined ratio in fy24 and also
Improvement of Roane Roe in High Teens
going forward
okay insurance is what is in focus on
the back of earnings well let's move on
to Pharma now standing by we have Aris
live Glenmark and Shelby in Focus
harmonic
has acquired nine of glenmarks
Dermatology brands in India for 340
crores the deal is at around 3.9 times
f522 trailing sales which is largely in
line with the previous deals which have
taken place in the domestic Market
recently now uh overall the acquisition
will be on a larger scale positive for
both companies for example eris's Doma
contribution will rise to 12.7 but the
street is not too enthused with the
matured sales of these Brands Glenmark
it's positive because the second this is
going to be the second sale of a
non-core asset in just about a month so
Glenmark is focused in terms of
divesting non-core assets so that's a
positive for Eris the numbers have been
weak so that's going to weigh Revenue
was up 27 but Standalone growth of
around nine and a half 40 missed
estimates versus a meeting growth
expectation and margins have reduced to
32 versus 36.6 year in year and a flat
on a q1 q basis as well uh shall be I
expect the stock to probably uh be in
the red because of margins Revenue was
up 25 but margins were 15 and a half
four percent versus Seventeen point four
percent year in year and versus 18 last
quarter but in terms of the hospital
business occupancies have risen to 43.2
percent versus 41 and a half four
percent implant business has done well
for them which is up 153 year in year so
that might remove the stain from the
margins but overall it may be a possible
red for Shelby as well as Ferris
okay possible red for Shelby and Aries
thanks a lot for that well Delta Corp
came out with its numbers and Tata
metallics also in Focus Nigel you're
watching both these things yeah let's go
with Tyler metallic since that's my core
sector well out there they had a blast
furnace shutdown for some part of the
past quarter but yet they delivered a
growth on the top line the problem is
margin Improvement was not as much as
anticipated it was up only around 30
Pips or so and the ebit number well on
the power business which is the the Big
Iron business which is the commoditized
business there was some improvement but
the street would have liked to see the
ductile iron pipes business and the ebit
out them has come in low on a sequential
basis as well as on a year in year basis
that's despite having volumes up by 10
to around 15 percent that said the
numbers are weak however quarter four
will be much better because the blast
furnace has revived volumes will pick up
and also you'll see greater flow in
terms of revenues moving to Delta Corp
seasonally very strong quarter was
supposed to be but on a sequential base
actually the numbers haven't shown any
growth on a year in your basis yes on
the top line they are higher but margins
are a bit of a disappointment the gaming
business while out there you had some
growth the margins though compressed out
them and there was continues to be
losses on both the hospitality business
as well as the online business so better
for disappointment in an otherwise
superb quarter was supposedly uh
supposed to come out from Delta Corp
going with red on both these two but
Vivek joins us to tell us about Eid
Parry as well as rvnl hi Vivek morning
well good morning you know a couple of
stops on the radar on the back of news
flow so Eid Parry a significant develop
in terms of the company managing the
comments operations at Andhra Pradesh
for a Distillery now you know this
particular Distillery has almost 120
kilo liters per day capacity so it's a
positive as far as the you know Eid
Parry is concerned a some more action
seen as far as the railway ordering is
concerned so rvnl and Siemens you know
have formed a Consortium and they've bid
for two projects and now they've
actually emerged as the lowest bid off
for two Metro Rail projects in Surat as
well as Ahmedabad now the value of the
Surat Metro Rail Project is close to a
little over 670 crore and the Ahmedabad
Metro Rail Project is valued over 380
crores now this particular Consortium
you know the comprises of Siemens and
rbnl is in the ratio of 65 to 35
respectively so watch out for some
positive green ticket on both of these
names all right thanks a lot for that
and thanks to our entire team in case
you missed out on any of those talks
here's the list for you uh the stocks
with positive news flow there's ITC
ICICI Prudential ICICI Lombard Glenmark
Pharma Eid Parry rvnl oil stocks with
negative news so this shall be Eris Life
Sciences Tata metallics and Delta Corp
but oil prices have been moving higher
in fact Brent food is now above 86
dollars a barrel on hopes of a China
demand rebound Manisha Gupta is here to
give us a quick Roundup of all that
she's tracking in that Arena Manisha
good morning
foreign
report that came in yesterday expects a
2023 demand to gain up by 2.2 million
barrels per day we also have seen strong
Chinese demand for the month of December
China trudim oil imports Rose by four
percent in December as compared to last
month and have been on the higher side
as compared to last year as well and
we've seen stronger amount of imports
for the petroleum products as well and
that clearly has been supportive markets
also turkey will keep an eye on the U.S
economic data that comes in and this
week you have retail sales uh
manufacturing activity all of those
numbers coming in the markets are taking
some support from that as well but not
just through the metal prices continue
to surge as well we have copper now
trading at a new seven month highs the
low Supply is increasing demand are some
of the supportive factors here as well
and not just copper aluminum zinc and
nickel also have seen gains overnight
markets are looking at some restocking
ahead of the China New Year lunar new
your holiday remember Chinese markets
are shot in the next week and there is
buying ahead of that too
all right Manisha thank you very much
for that uh so that's the action as far
as commodity markets are concerned we'll
take a very quick break here the event
choksy of KR chokes you will be joining
in uh for some fundamental stop talk uh
later we'll have a lot of commentary
coming in from the world economic Forum
which is underway in Davao Switzerland
uh and of course we'll play out some
important interesting sound bites from
the managements of companies like Apollo
tires paytm by juice and many more stay
with us
[Music]
foreign